Alright, guys, for our next shine what we're going to teach you is called a Tightrope.
Okay?
Take a look, I'm going to start off with a basic, five, six, basic.
One, two, three, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, five, six, basic.
One, two, three, five, and stop.
Let me demonstrate it from the back.
With a basic, five, six and one, two, three, five, six, seven.
One, two, three, five, six, basic, one, two, three, five, and stop.
Okay?
So, let's break it down for you guys.
We're going to cross over in front on one.
Guys, we're also going to cross again on two with our right leg, and cross again on three.
What's really important here, guys, is that you use your hips.
Okay?
Don't think it's nothing feminine, it's just trying to get your feet around.
So again, using your hips guys, with our arms at home base, we're going to cross on one, cross two, cross three.
Now the biggest thing here, also, guys, remember, stay on the balls of your feet.
Try not to stay flat-footed, because that's going to be easy to trip yourself on the pattern.
So here we go.
Nice and slow.
Cross on one, cross on two, cross on three, pause on four.
Right here, guys, we're going to continue to do it for three more counts.
Cross on five, cross on six, cross on seven.
Go right into our basic.
One, two, three, five, six, seven.
Okay?
So let me demonstrate it one more time for you guys.
Maybe I should do it this way.
Five, six, basic.
One, two, three, five, six, seven.
Cross, cross, cross.
Five, six, seven.
Basic, one, two, three, five, and stop.
Now remember guys, with your arms, again we want to keep them right here at home base, just going opposite your feet, and keep them right here, strong.
Okay?
Thank you, guys.